btcprivate.org 2018-06-05

# Bitcoin Private

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of [https://btcprivate.org](https://btcprivate.org/) (the “Website”). We use your personal information to better understand your usage of the site, and to collect traffic statistics.

By using the site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

  1. Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Website ("Log Data"). The information collected in the Website’s Log Data may include, but is not limited to, your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address (with replaced last byte), browser type, browser version, the pages of the Website you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

  2. Cookies

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Website.

We may use cookies for the following purposes:

      1. To keep track of whether you have pressed the "OK" button on the cookie disclaimer, so we don't bother you with the notification if you have.
      2. Our analytics software (Google Analytics) uses cookies to measure and better understand user-interactions on our Website. You can read more about how Google Analytics uses cookies [here](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage).
  3. Google Analytics

We use a third-party JavaScript plug-in provided by Google called "Google Analytics" to provide us with useful traffic statistics and to better understand how you use our site. We do not have direct access to the information obtained from Google Analytics, but Google provides us with a summary through their dashboard.

We may share the information obtained from Google Analytics with business partners who are interested in advertising on our website. The information shared with these business partners will not contain any personally identifying information (Google does not provide us with direct access to the data and therefore we cannot see this information).

Bitcoin Private truly values the privacy of our users who visit our Website– that is why we allow for our users the freedom to opt-out of having your information collected by Google Analytics by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on provided by Google [here](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/google-analytics-opt-out/fllaojicojecljbmefodhfapmkghcbnh?hl=en). This will prevent your information being used by Google Analytics. Doing this will not affect your ability to use our Website in any way.

  4. Contact Us

If you have any questions about Bitcoin Private’s Privacy Policy, or how your data is being collected and processed, please feel free to submit your inquiries on [GitHub](https://github.com/BTCPrivate/BitcoinPrivate).

  5. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Bitcoin Private may update this Privacy Policy from time to time when necessary. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new privacy policy on our Website. We strongly advise that our users review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

  6. Last amendment

This disclaimer was drafted and published for the first time on February 24, 2018. There have been no amendments to this disclaimer.
